ABDUL WAHAB

CONTACT #: +92-333-6364975

EMAIL: engr.awkhokhar@gmail.com

ADDRESS: House # 2, Street # 3, Link Ferozepur Road, Lahore

OBJECTIVE:

An engineering graduate with certification in educational management from **LUMS**, passion for STEM with experience of 10 years including 4 years in teaching is looking for a position where I can instill thirst for knowledge in students to prepare them for a challenging future.

AREA OF EXPERTISE:

Administration Academic Research Trainings

Physics Mathematics Health & Safety

Budgeting & Costing Procurement & Coordination IT Skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

COMPANY	DESIGNATION	TIME PERIOD
Vertex Electronics Pvt. Limited	AM (Engg Solutions I&C)	Oct 2016 – Till Date
CAP Engineering Co.	Sr. Engineer (Application)	Dec 2014 – Oct 2016
Lahore Polytechnic Institute	Head of Department (Electrical)	Sept 2010 – Nov 2014
Private Tutoring	Beacon House Defense Campus Students	2011-2015

EDUCATION:

INSTITUE	DEGREE & CERTIFICATIONS	TIME PERIOD
ITH Labora	NAC Electrical Engineering	2010. Cantinus
ITU, Lahore	MS Electrical Engineering	2019- Continue
LUMS	Educational Management	2018 – 2019 (2 M)
The Islamia University of BWP	B.Sc. Electronics Engineering	2004 – 2008
Govt. Degree College, Sadiqabad	F.Sc. Pre-Engineering	2002 – 2004
Pak Grammar High School	Matriculation	2000 – 2002

EXHIBITIONS & EVENT MANAGEMENT:

POGEE-2018 held at Expo Centre, Lahore

Sundar Industrial Exhibitions-2018 held at S.I.E, Lahore & 2019 held at Expo Centre, Lahore Electricity Exhibition-2019 held at Expo Centre, Lahore

COMPUTER SKILLS:

Microsoft Office (Outlook, Excel, Word, Power Point)

Microsoft Windows (XP, win 7, win 8.1, win 10)

Working knowledge of Instrumentation Selection Tools by Emerson Rosemount, Siemens, Endress Hauser Applicator, INSTRUCALC ETC

REFERENCES:

Will be furnished on demand.

